Our hero, our hero, claims a warrior's heart.
英雄啊 英雄啊 战斗号角已经响起
I tell you, I tell you, the Dragonborn comes.
就是您 就是您 龙裔已经归来了啊
With a Voice wielding power of the ancient Nord art.
期待着古诺德血液中那龙之咆哮的苏醒。
Believe, believe the Dragonborn comes.
我们坚信 坚信龙裔已经降临
It's an end to the evil, of all Skyrim's foes.
这是我们在天际的水深火热中的救赎
Beware, beware, the Dragonborn comes.
不要畏惧 不要退后 龙裔已经到来
For the darkness has passed, and the legend yet grows.
黑暗即将退去 传奇就将开始
You'll know, You'll know the Dragonborn's come.
你会明白 明白龙裔存在的意义。
Dovahkiin! Dovahkiin!  Naal ok zin los
龙裔! 龙裔!以他的荣誉宣誓!
vahrii wah dein vokul mahfaeraak ahst vaal
永远把罪恶扼杀在摇篮!
ahrk fin norok paal graan
凶猛的敌人开始溃败
Fod nust hon zindro zaan
当他们听到我们胜利的怒吼后
Dovahkiin, fah hin ,kogaan mu draal.
龙裔给予我们祈祷后的祝福
You should have acted
你必须行动起来
They're already there
它们正在到来
The Elder Scrolls told them return
上古卷轴召唤它们归来
Their defeat was merely a delay
打败它们经不起耽搁
To the time after Oblivion opened
在湮灭之门开启后
When the Sons of Skyrim would spill their own blood
当天际之子洒下自己的鲜血时
But no one wanted to believe
但却无人愿意去相信
Believe they even existed
去相信它们依然存在
And when the truth finally dawns
但当真相最终揭晓时
It dawns in fire!
他们见到的之后火焰
But there's one they fear
但是 还有一样令他们害怕的东西
In their tongue,he is Dovahkiin---DragonBorn
在龙语中读作Dovahkiin---龙裔
力量, 平衡, 推动
Fus, Ro, Dah
不认输
变成龙
让民主
照万国
望苍天
站在苍天中
星魂白
踏破宇宙
Dovahkiin Dovahkiin
让它星魂洒地
何为难 何为苦
抛向大海百川
捍卫国 捍卫家
我们雄心挑战
踏大地 打大帝
我们感恩未来
战! 战! 战! 喝呀